export const exercise1=[
{
		"question":1,
		"exercise":"Good morning",
		"answer":"Ị bọọla chi",
		"subquestion":""
		},
		{
		"question":2,
		"exercise":"Do you have a free room?",
		"answer":". Ohere ọ dị n’ụlọ oriri na nkwari akụ unu? ",
		"subquestion":""
		},
		{
		"question":3,
		"exercise":"What will you like to have?",
		"answer":"Gini ka ị chọrọ?",
		"subquestion":""
		},
		{
		"question":4,
		"exercise":"Give me a call.",
		"answer":"Kpọọ m n’ekwentị,  ",
		"subquestion":""
		},
		{
		"question":5,
		"exercise":"The bill please.",
		"answer":"Ego ole ka m ga akwụ?",
		"subquestion":""
		}
]
export const exercise2=[
{
		"question":1,
		"exercise":"My name is  ",
		"answer":"Aha m bụ ",
		"subquestion":""
		},
		{
		"question":2,
		"exercise":"I am twenty five years old.",
		"answer":"Adị m afọ iri abụọ na ise, ",
		"subquestion":""
		},
		{
		"question":3,
		"exercise":"I am dark in complexion.",
		"answer":"Adị m oji.",
		"subquestion":""
		},
		{
		"question":4,
		"exercise":"I am handsome.",
		"answer":"amara m mma,  ",
		"subquestion":""
		},
		{
		"question":5,
		"exercise":"I am tall and beautiful.",
		"answer":"Etoro m ogologo maa kwa mma.",
		"subquestion":""
		}
]
export const exercise3=[
{
		"question":1,
		"exercise":"",
		"answer":"Mgbede",
		"subquestion":"ọma (good evening)"
		},
		{
		"question":2,
		"exercise":"Onye a ",
		"answer":"Bụ mazi Adeshola",
		"subquestion":"(here is Mr. Adesola)"
		},
		{
		"question":3,
		"exercise":"",
		"answer":"Nnọọ, ",
		"subquestion":"ebe a bụ Lagos.( welcome to Lagos)"
		},
		{
		"question":4,
		"exercise":"Ebee",
		"answer":"ka i si ",
		"subquestion":"? ( where do you come from?)"
		},
		
]
export const exercise4=[
{
		"question":1,
		"exercise":"There is no metro here.",
		"answer":"Enweghi ọdọ ụgbọ",
		"subquestion":"na-agba n’okpuru ala ebe a."
		},
		{
		"question":2,
		"exercise":"The train station is in front.",
		"answer":"ọdọ ụgbọoloko",
		"subquestion":"nọ n’ihu."
		},
		{
		"question":3,
		"exercise":"Thank you for the information. Imeela maka",
		"answer":"itụziri m aka",
		"subquestion":""
		},
		{
		"question":4,
		"exercise":"Go straight Gaa ",
		"answer":" . n’ogologo ụzọ",
		"subquestion":""
		},
		{
		"question":5,
		"exercise":"You are at the train station.Ị nọ na ọdọ",
		"answer":"ụgbọoloko.",
		"subquestion":""
		}
]
export const exercise5=[
{
		"question":1,
		"exercise":"What are you doing today?",
		"answer":"Gịnị ka, ",
		"subquestion":"ị na eme taa?"
		},
		{
		"question":2,
		"exercise":"I am going for shopping.Ana m aga ",
		"answer":"ịzụ ihe, ",
		"subquestion":""
		},
		{
		"question":3,
		"exercise":"Are you going alone? Ị ga-iga ",
		"answer":"Naanị gị, ",
		"subquestion":""
		},
		{
		"question":4,
		"exercise":"Kelechi is coming with me.",
		"answer":"Mụ na,  ",
		"subquestion":"kelechi so aga."
		},
		{
		"question":5,
		"exercise":"We will buy shoes and phones Anyị ga azụ",
		"answer":"akpụkpọ ụkwụ .",
		"subquestion":"na ekwentị"
		}
]
export const exercise6=[
{
		"question":1,
		"exercise":"What do you want to be",
		"answer":"Kedụ ihe ichọrọ ị bụ?",
		"subquestion":""
		},
		{
		"question":2,
		"exercise":"I want to be a nurse",
		"answer":"Achọrọ m ị bụ nọsụ.",
		"subquestion":""
		},
		{
		"question":3,
		"exercise":"My father is a doctor",
		"answer":"Nna m bụ dọkịta. ",
		"subquestion":""
		},
		{
		"question":4,
		"exercise":"I like the profession",
		"answer":"Akaọrụ ahụ na-amasị m.",
		"subquestion":""
		},
		{
		"question":5,
		"exercise":"Goodluck",
		"answer":"Nwee iru ọma.",
		"subquestion":""
		}
]
export const exercise7=[
{
		"question":1,
		"exercise":"How old are you?",
		"answer":"Afọ ole ka, ,",
		"subquestion":"ka ị dị?"
		},
		{
		"question":2,
		"exercise":"When is your birthday? Kedụ ụbọchi ncheta",
		"answer":"Ọmụmụ gị?",
		"subquestion":"?"
		},
		{
		"question":3,
		"exercise":"I want to celebrate my birthday in the princes’ garden.",
		"answer":"Achọ®ọ m i mee, ",
		"subquestion":"mmemme ncheta ọmụmụ m na The Garden of Princes."
		},
		{
		"question":4,
		"exercise":"How many people are you inviting?",
		"answer":"Mmadụ ole, ",
		"subquestion":"ka ị ga-akpọ ka ha bịa."
		},
		{
		"question":5,
		"exercise":"Happy birthday in advance.",
		"answer":"Obi ụtọ ncheta.",
		"subquestion":"ọmụmụ n’ọdị n’ihu."
		}
]
export const exercise8=[
{
		"question":1,
		"exercise":"Ọ bụ ",
		"answer":"naani ya ",
		"subquestion":"bụ nwanne m nwaanyị."
		},
		{
		"question":2,
		"exercise":"Ụmụnne m nwoke atọ ",
		"answer":"alụọla nwunye,",
		"subquestion":""
		},
		{
		"question":3,
		"exercise":"Nwanne m nwaanyị nke obere alụbeghị di.",
		"answer":"alụbeghị di, ",
		"subquestion":""
		},
		{
		"question":4,
		"exercise":"Nne m na nna m agbasaala.",
		"answer":" Agbasaala, ",
		"subquestion":""
		},
		{
		"question":5,
		"exercise":"Abụ m onye tọchara ndị ọzọ n’ezi n’ụlọ anyị",
		"answer":"onye tọchara ndị ọzọ.",
		"subquestion":""
		}
]
export const exercise9=[
{
		"question":1,
		"exercise":"It is raining and i have no umbrella",
		"answer":"Mmiri na ezo",
		"subquestion":"ma e jighi m nche anwụ."
		},
		{
		"question":2,
		"exercise":"I is tiring going for an outing Ọ na-",
		"answer":"Agwụ m ike",
		"subquestion":"i kpagarị."
		},
		{
		"question":3,
		"exercise":"Lets go for a walk Ka anyị",
		"answer":"Ga kpagarịtu",
		"subquestion":""
		},
		{
		"question":4,
		"exercise":"Dont you want to drink a beer?",
		"answer":"Ọ bụ na-ichoghị ",
		"subquestion":"ịṅụ beer"
		},
		{
		"question":5,
		"exercise":"Let us stay home.Ka anyị",
		"answer":"Nọrọ n’ụlọ.",
		"subquestion":""
		}
]
export const exercise10=[
{
		"question":1,
		"exercise":"Anyị aga aganwu na?",
		"answer":"Sirima",
		"subquestion":""
		},
		{
		"question":2,
		"exercise":"Bọọlụ ụkwụ na ",
		"answer":"Amasị m",
		"subquestion":""
		},
		{
		"question":3,
		"exercise":"Ka anyị lele ",
		"answer":"Ihe onyonyo",
		"subquestion":""
		},
		{
		"question":4,
		"exercise":"",
		"answer":"Atụmaatụ ",
		"subquestion":"ọma."
		},
		{
		"question":5,
		"exercise":"Ka anyị tụọ  ",
		"answer":"agba tennis",
		"subquestion":""
		}
]
